I drive better drunk, you know?
(Jimmy:)It makes you pay attention.
(Leonard:)No. Come on in.
I'll make you a cup of coffee.
- I wouldn't be imposing?
- No.
(Leonard:)Yes.
- Sheldon, we can't let him drive.
- Then take away his keys...
(Sheldon:)...and make him wander the streets
with the other drunks.
(Leonard:)You remember Sheldon, and Raj,
and Howard.
(Jimmy:)Not really, no.
It's funny, huh? Back in school,
I was the winner, and you were the loser.
(Jimmy:)And now we're reversed.
(Jimmy:)You're the winner.
(Sheldon:)You'd think a winner
could make a decent cup of cocoa.
(Jimmy:)- Mind if I use your bathroom?
- Yeah. It's just back there.
(Howard:)How about that?
After all these years...
...your big, bad high-school bully
finally apologizes.
(Leonard:)Yeah. It kind of rekindles your faith
in the basic goodness in people.